Customers want
one fair price
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
so my husband
I have five kids
and they're all
driving now
which is insane
our insurance
bill every month
is like a
mortgage
It's just the
craziest thing
so we've done a
lot of car
shopping recently
and we really
prefer to go to
places just as
customers where
there's the price
for the car and
the price is what
you get
You have these
places where it
looks higher
but then there's
room for
finagling and
haggling and
wiggle room
And then there's
other places
where they don't
haggle
It's just a
price
It's a really
fair price
So we really
prefer to go to
the no haggle
places And I
think the same
goes true for not
everyone
but most of your
customers are
looking for the
same thing
They're just
looking for
transparency
They're looking
for trust